Guide to the Organization of Staff Analysts Records WAG.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files
  - Comptroller's Office: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Conference: General, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Conference: Packet, Jun 13, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Conference: Preparation materials, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Contract: First Bargaining Contract between the City Of New York and the Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Contract: Second Bargaining Contract between the City Of New York and the Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Contract: Third Bargaining Contract between the City Of New York and the Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Contract: Fourth Collective Bargaining Contract between the City Of New York and the Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Contract: Fourth Collective Bargaining Contract between the City Of New York and the Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Contract: Staff Analysts et al. Revised and Proposed Contract as of December 10, 1998, Dec 10, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Contract Demands, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Contract Demands: Copy from notebook, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Contract Demands: From memo to members, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Contract Demands, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Contract Introductions: First, Second, Third and Fifth Bargaining Contracts, 1965-1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Contracting Out: A workbook presentation, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Birthwright, Kaet/President, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Brodsky, Rochelle/President, Chairperson, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Council of Personnel Examiners (COPE), 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: "Early Years", 1978 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: Cunningham, Richard/Treasurer, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Denial of benefits for Judith Layzer, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Exam Complaints, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: 5x8 File Problem at K7, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Furloughs, Leaves, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: General, 1980s-2000s (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Kiok, Joan Stern/Attorney, 1980s-2000s (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence: Lutenberg, Marvin, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence: Mail order prescription "horror stories" and related materials, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence: Mullgraw, Susan/Chairperson, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: One-in-Three Rule, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Palumbo, Guy B./ Chairperson, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Promotions (with Civil Service Lists), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Rule 6/1/9, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cost-of-Living Adjustment (COLA), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: As Chair of OSA Petition Against New York City Off-Track Betting, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Charges of "Absent without authorization", 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Discussion Regarding the Analyst Series Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) Local 371, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/"Administrative Politics of the Closing of the Mott Haven SSC in the New York Department of Social Services by George P. Cronin (1972) and related materials, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/City Wide Contract between the Communication Workers of America (CWA) and The City of New York, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/general (including Croghan as Democratic State Committeeman), 1960s (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/general (including resume materials from 1975 and materials on Work Relief Employment Program (WREP), 1970s (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/general, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/Proposed Contract between The Staff (Union) and SSEU-371 (Employer), undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/The Unionist Xerox copies, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/ The Unionist Xerox copies, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Early files/Zip Coding the Welfare System, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Exhibits for Staff Analysts CBU 180 - 1% Equity, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: File entitled "Expulsion of Bob" includes correspondence, petitions and decision, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Croghan, Robert J.:General (includes some handwritten materials), undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Handwritten materials - loose notes, lists, figures, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: "The 1967 Welfare [SSEU] Strike (A Case History)", undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Promotion Exams #7512 (Administrative Staff Analyst) and #8578 (Administrative Manager)/Letter and Exhibits, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Interview with Michael Nash (NYU), undated; 2 folders 2 digibeta tapes (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: "Report Report", Jul 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Time and Activity Sheets, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Weekly Planners, 1991, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson (President): "Affiliations", 1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson (President): Correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson (President): Correspondence, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence and related materials regarding the Analyst Exams for 2004 and 2005 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Croghan, Robert J., Chairperson: Correspondence preparing for negotiations, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Croghan, Robert J, Chairperson: Correspondence re: Revising Qualification Requirements, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Croghan, Robert J.: from Joan Kiok "for your review", 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Croghan, Robert J, Chairperson: Negotiation petitions and correspondence, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Defining "Disability" under the ADA (Americans' with Disabilities Act): Revised and Expanded 1997 Edition (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dental Plan Experience Report, Jul 1, 1989-Jun 30, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Dental Program (SSEU), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Department of Business Services: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Department of City Planning, City of New York: Absence Control Program, Mar 1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Department of City Planning, City of New York: Equal Opportunity Informational Guide Fiscal Year 1993, Dec 1992 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Department of City Planning, City of New York: Law on Conflicts of Interests, Mar 1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Department of City Planning, City of New York: Smoking Pollution Control Department, Feb 1989 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Department of City Planning, City of New York: Standards of Conduct and Disciplinary Procedures, Jun 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Department of Consumer Affairs: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Department of Employment: Timekeeping Pilot Procedure, Oct 31, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Department of General Services (DGS): Request for Proposals (RFPs) for Tenant Representative Services and Architectural, Interior and Engineering Design Services (Contracting out), Oct 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Department of Personnel: Affirmative Employment Plan/Draft and OSA Statement, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Department of Personnel: Appendix VI-Agency Guide to Performance Evaluation for Sub-Managerial Positions, May 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Department of Personnel: City Personnel Director Rules, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Department of Personnel: Determinations of the City Personnel Director, May 13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Department of Personnel: General, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Department of Personnel: Information for Employees Being Separated from City Service, Nov 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Department of Personnel: Layoff Procedures, Nov 1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Department of Personnel: Layoffs-Cohn, Sheldon Correspondence, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Department of Personnel: Layoffs-correspondence notices and lists, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Department of Personnel: Layoffs General, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Department of Personnel: Leave Regulations: For Employees who are under the Career and Salary Plan, Oct 1977 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Department of Personnel: Leave Regulations: For Employees who are under the Career and Salary Plan, May 1980 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Department of Personnel: Leave Regulations: For Management Employees, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Department of Personnel: Leave Regulations (Retirement Leave Option): For Employees Who Are under the Career and Salary Plan, Jan 1975 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Department of Personnel: Personnel Policy and Procedure Bulletins, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Department of Personnel: Proposal 81-2 to delete or broadband, Jan 7, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Department of Personnel: Redeployment Procedures, Jun 21, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Department of Personnel: Rule 6.1.9, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Department of Social Services: Human Resources Administration Office of Personnel Services Title Listing, Jun 1981 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Directory: Central Office, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Directory: Central Office Personnel, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Directory: Coney Island Hospital, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Directory: Elmhurst Hospital Center, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Directory: Kings County Hospital, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Directory: New York City Transit (includes Job Vacancy Notices), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Directory: Queens Hospital Center, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Directory: Queens Hospital Center, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Directory: TBTA Interoffice by Department, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Directory: Woodhull Hospital, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - District Council 37: Anniversary Program, Oct 21, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - District Council 37: General, undated, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - District Council 37: Press Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - District Council 37: Re: RU-710-79 and RU-730B-79 - Systems Analysts List from Local 1407, Nov 10, 1963, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - District Council 37: Special File Listing-Staff Analysts, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - District Council 37: Special File Listing-Staff Analysts, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - District Council 37 Research & Negotiations Department: Citywide Demands Status Report:, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Dollar for a Decent New York, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Partners, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Domestic Partners, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Domestic Partners, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Domestic Violence Workplace Education Day, Sep 27, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dues Check-off Authorization, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Dues Refunds: Part Timers, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Earnings Records: Julia Jorge, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: "A Choice of Health Plans" for New York City Employees and Retirees under age 65, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials (including SSEU Local 371 Benefits Fund Plan Book), 1981, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials (including New York City program), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials (including New York City program), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials (including Benefits Booklet for the Management Benefits Fund), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials (including NYC Summary Program Description), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Employee Benefits Programs: general materials, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Exams: Appeals, Dec 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Exams: Associate Staff Analyst (Personnel) No. 2584, Associate Staff Analyst (Organizational Research) No. 2581, Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) No. 2588, held in March 1997 -- Appointment Screening Logs (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Exams: Associate Staff Analyst (Personnel) No. 2584, Associate Staff Analyst (Organizational Research) No. 2581, Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) No. 2588, held in March 1997 - City Certification, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Exams: Associate Staff Analyst (Personnel) No. 2584, Associate Staff Analyst (Organizational Research) No. 2581, Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) No. 2588, held in March 1997 - Correspondence and Lists (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Exams: Associate Staff Analyst (Personnel) No. 2584, Associate Staff Analyst (Organizational Research) No. 2581, Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) No. 2588, held in March 1997 - Correspondence and Lists, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Exams: Associate Staff Analyst (Personnel) No. 2584, Associate Staff Analyst (Organizational Research) No. 2581, Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) No. 2588, held in March 1997 - Correspondence and Lists including Sheila Gorsky FOIL (Freedom of Information Law) Request, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Exams: Associate Staff Analyst (Personnel) No. 2584, Associate Staff Analyst (Organizational Research) No. 2581, Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) No. 2588, held in March 1997 - Job Vacancy Postings and Pool Schedules (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Exams: Experience and Education Exam, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Exams: General, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Exams: General, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Exams: Notices of Examination, 1990s-2000s (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Exams: Promotion to Administrative Staff Analyst Exam No. 2549, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Exams: Promotion to Administrative Staff Analyst Exam No. 7512, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Exams: Promotion to Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) Exam No. 2581 Answer Key, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Exams: Promotion to Associate Staff Analyst (Budget) Exam No. 2581 Notice of Examination, correspondence post exam, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Exams: Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) Examination No. 7669 - Promotion to Assistant Director (Welfare), Apr 13, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Exams: Staff Analyst, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Exams: Training/Practice, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Executed Agreement: Apr 1, 1995-Mar 31, 2000 Supplemental Agreement, Jan 2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Executed Contract: Citywide Agreement, Jul 1, 1985-Jun 30, 1987, Sep 29, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Executed Contract: Citywide Agreement, Jul 1, 1990-Jun 30, 1992, Aug 13, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Executed Contract: Oct 1, 1990-Dec 31, 1991, Mar 31, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Executed Contract: Jan 1, 1992-Mar 31, 1995, Dec 28, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Executed Contract: Apr 1, 1995-Mar 31, 2000, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Executed Contract: Apr 1, 2000-Jun 30, 2002, Dec 27, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Executed Contract: Staff Analysts et al, Term: Apr 1, 2000-Jun 30, 2002, Feb 25, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Executive Order #107: Procedures for Orderly Payroll Check-off of Union Dues and Agency Shop Fees, Dec 29, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Expense Records: Borges, Gladiolo, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Expense Records: Extra-Ordinary Expenses (American Express) (Collective Bargaining), 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Expense Records: Jorge, Julia, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Expense Records: Joseph, Terry & Andy, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Expense Records: Knight, Patrick, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Expense Records: McKeon, Jim, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Expense Records: Serlin, Anthony, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Expense Records: Sperling, Joe, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Expense Records: Williams, Nathaniel, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Family and Medical Leave Act of 1993: Application of FMLA to City's Time and Leave Rules, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies (FPWA): "Welfare Reform and Its Impact in the Nation and in New York, Aug 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Filing of Financial Disclosure Reports with the [City of New York] Conflicts of Interest Board, Feb 21, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Financial: General, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Financial Plan: City of New York Fiscal Years 2002-2006, Feb 13, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statement, Jan 1, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 31, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statements, Dec 2003 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Forms: Blank, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Forms: Personnel, Employee, undated, 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Frequency Chart for the City Start Date of Members of OSA, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Furlough Survey, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - General, undated, 1970s-2000s (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - General: "Early Years" file, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Gorsky, Sheila: Administrative Staff Analyst Result Cards, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Gorsky, Sheila: Correspondence, 1980s (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Gorsky, Sheila: Correspondence, 1990s (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Gorsky, Sheila: Correspondence, 2000s (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Gorsky, Sheila: General, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Gorsky, Sheila: Sale of time in lieu of overtime rule, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al: Notice of Petition for a Judgment pursuant to Article 78 of the Civil Practice Law and Rules, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al v. Juan U. Ortiz et al re: use of Analyst List: correspondence and related materials (Committee to Move the List), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al v. Juan U. Ortiz et al re: use of Analyst List: correspondence and related materials, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al v. Juan U. Ortiz et al re: use of Analyst List: Joan Stern Kiok (Attorney) agreement, Jun 27, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al v. Juan U. Ortiz et al re: use of Analyst List: Legal Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al v. Juan U. Ortiz et al re: use of Analyst List: Lists, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Gorsky, Sheila et al v. Juan U. Ortiz et al re: use of Analyst List: Settlement Offer, Jun 29, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Green Files: List, Jun 10, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Grievance Summaries, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Grievance Summaries, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Grievance Summaries, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Grievance Summaries, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Grievance Summaries, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Grievances, 1990s-2000s (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Grievances: Bronx BCW (Bureau of Child Welfare), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Grievances: Bronx BCW (Bureau of Child Welfare), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Grievances: Bronx BCW (Bureau of Child Welfare), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Grievances: Bronx BCW (Bureau of Child Welfare), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Grievances: Bronx BCW (Bureau of Child Welfare), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Grievances: Brooklyn BCW (Bureau of Child Welfare), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Grievances: Disciplinary Process, undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Guide for New York City Managerial Employees, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Health and Retirement Plans: General Information Pamphlets, 1960s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hershey Solidarity News, Jun 5, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - History of the OSA [to 1991?], undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Huertas, James v. Michael J. Codd as Police Commissioner of the City of New York et al: Notice of Motion, Index No. 05815/76, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Human Resources: Absence Control Procedure, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Human Resources: CCSS/DSS Personnel Roster, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Human Resources: General, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Human Resources: Guidelines, 1970s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Human Resources: Job Vacancy Notices and Citywide Recruitment Flyers, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Human Resources: Job Vacancy Notices and Citywide Recruitment Flyers, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Human Resources: Listing for OSA of Active Analysts, Oct 2, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Human Resources: Severance Incentive Program, Apr 18, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Human Resources: Supervision of Employee Attendance and Punctuality, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Human Resources: Unionization of All Staff and Associate Staff Analysts, Jun 16, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Improper Practice (Unfair Labor Practice) Concerning Managerial/Confidential Employees, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)